{
  "questions": [
    {
      "id": "1",
      "prompt": "What special prop should always be included for lists of elements?",
      "answers": [
        "id",
        "name",
        "key",
        "prop"
      ],
      "correctIndex": 2
    },
    {
      "id": "2",
      "prompt": "A React component is a function that returns ______.",
      "answers": [
        "HTML",
        "JSX",
        "props",
        "state"
      ],
      "correctIndex": 1
    },
    {
      "id": "3",
      "prompt": "Which event handler will run when a user is finished filling out a form?",
      "answers": [
        "onSubmit",
        "onClick",
        "onChange",
        "onForm"
      ],
      "correctIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "id": "4",
      "prompt": "______ is a tool that transpiles JSX into valid JavaScript.",
      "answers": [
        "React",
        "Babel",
        "Webpack",
        "ES6"
      ],
      "correctIndex": 1
    },
    {
      "id": "5",
      "prompt": "What syntax makes it possible to unpack values from arrays, or properties from objects, into distinct variables?",
      "answers": [
        "spread",
        "key-value",
        "coalescing",
        "destructuring"
      ],
      "correctIndex": 3
    },
    {
      "id": "6",
      "prompt": "Returning different elements from a component depending on the state of your application is known as _____ rendering.",
      "answers": [
        "voodoo",
        "conditional",
        "reactive",
        "controlled"
      ],
      "correctIndex": 1
    },
    {
      "id": "98b0",
      "prompt": "",
      "answers": [
        "",
        "",
        "",
        ""
      ],
      "correctIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "id": "0de3",
      "prompt": "",
      "answers": [
        "",
        "",
        "",
        ""
      ],
      "correctIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "id": "69a4",
      "prompt": "",
      "answers": [
        "",
        "",
        "",
        ""
      ],
      "correctIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "id": "9a90",
      "prompt": "what is a prop",
      "answers": [
        "",
        "",
        "",
        ""
      ],
      "correctIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "id": "075a",
      "prompt": "what is a prop",
      "answers": [
        "",
        "",
        "",
        ""
      ],
      "correctIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "id": "fffa",
      "prompt": "A react component is a function that returns ",
      "answers": [
        "html",
        "jsx",
        "props",
        "state"
      ],
      "correctIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "id": "42eb",
      "prompt": "A react component is a function that returns ",
      "answers": [
        "html",
        "jsx",
        "props",
        "state"
      ],
      "correctIndex": 0
    }
  ]
}